https://www.iti-global.com/privacy

Leadership
Meet the members of our leadership team.
CAREERS
We are seeking engineers who enjoy working in a flexible environment with opportunity for growth. Join us
License Utilities
Gather machine information needed to create a license code.
DATA TRANSMISSION
Securely share files with ITI.
CUSTOMER SUCCESS
Automation
Data Exchange and Process Automation Case Studies
Conversion
CAD File Conversion, Translation, Repair and Defeaturing Case Studies
09/14 - 09/16
ITI will be participating virtually at COExperience on September 14 - 16. Register
More Events >
PRESS RELEASES
International Technegroup Incorporated (ITI) is presenting virtually this year at Autodesk University 2020, November 16-20, 2020. ITI will have a few presentations on our Autodesk GoToINVENTOR solution powered by ITI.
Read More >
PRESS RELEASES
Autodesk University, November 16-20, 2020 – International Technegroup Limited (ITI), the global leader specializing in feature-based translation that enables the transfer of complete design intelligence from major CAD systems to INVENTOR with up to 100% automation and enhanced efficiency.
Read More >
White Papers
Download white papers created by ITI that can help you clear your interoperability obstacles.
ARTICLES
Read articles in the media that feature ITI and our solutions.
ITI Privacy Policy
EFFECTIVE DATE: MAY 17, 2018
As used in this “Privacy Policy”, “ITI” refers to all websites (including https://www.iti-global.com and http://info.iti-global.com), properties, and services owned or operated by International TechneGroup Incorporated, International TechneGroup ltd, or “ITI”.
This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of ITI. It explains when and how ITI collects end user and client information, including Personally Identifiable Information (defined below), how we use such information, and the circumstances under which we may disclose such information to others. This Privacy Policy includes the policies that ITI observes for compliance with laws in the United States as well as other applicable laws, including those followed regarding the transfer of Personally Identifiable Information from the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and/or Switzerland to the United States under the U.S. – EU Privacy Shield and U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor, respectively (collectively, the “Safe Harbor and Privacy Shield”).
By visiting the ITI website or blog, or registering for our service, you acknowledge that you accept and consent to the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.
What Types of User Information Does ITI Obtain?
Visitors to the ITI Website. If you are a visitor to the ITI website or a ITI client (“Client”) who registers or signs into the ITI website (including for purposes of obtaining a free trial of ITI services), we may obtain the following types of information from you or concerning your computer or device (“ITI Client Information”), which may include information that can itself be used to identify and/or contact you (“Personally Identifiable Information”):
Name
Email address
Phone number
Website name and URL
Visitor site preferences
ITI may also receive certain information that may be provided by your browser or mobile device, including:
Browser information
Operating system information
Mobile device information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.)
IP address
Pages accessed
Time of visit
Time of last visit
Referring site, application, or service, including the relevant search queries that led you to ITI’s website.
Visitors to the ITI Blog. If you wish to access certain functions within the ITI Blog, such as posting comments or registering for webinars, we may ask you to provide information, including:
Name
Title
Company
Country
Email address
Phone
Your website
How Do We Use This Information?
Visitors to the ITI Website. We use the ITI Client Information, including Personally Identifiable Information, to register your account, fulfill your requests, understand how you are engaging with ITI, communicate with you, determine if you are satisfied with the Service, and personalize your experience on the ITI website.
Visitors to the ITI Blog. We may use information you voluntarily provide when visiting the ITI blog to send you e-mail communications, such as information on upcoming webinars.
ITI does not collect or aggregate information about end user behavior across multiple, different websites that are operated by different Clients, nor does it use any Client User Data for purposes of behavioral advertising. However, ITI may analyze Client User Data in the aggregate for purposes of internal research and/or to determine overall trends or metrics concerning how users are engaging with us, and may report such general trends publicly, without disclosing any Client User Data.
ITI Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
Cookies. ITI uses cookies (small text files that ITI stores locally on your computer) for one or more of the following purposes: to help identify unique visitors and/or devices; assess usage patterns and perform traffic analysis; identify visitor preferences; conduct A/B testing; diagnose problems with our servers, and otherwise administer ITI Services. ITI does not use methods such as browser cache, Flash cookies, or eTags, for acquiring or storing information about end users web browsing activity on Client websites or otherwise.
If you do not wish to have ITI place and use cookies on your computer, you should set your browser preferences to refuse all cookies before accessing ITI websites. ITI is not responsible for any failure by you or your browser to accurately implement or communicate your browser preferences or settings. However, your rejection of all cookies will prevent ITI from determining whether or not someone using your computer has previously visited the website, i.e., whether or not the visitor is a “unique” visitor, and from retrieving any information about your prior activities through information contained in a cookie.
Please note that if you set your browser to reject cookies, some features of the websites you visit may be unavailable. For more information on how to reject cookies, see your browser's instructions on changing your cookie settings.
If you do not elect to set your browser preferences to refuse cookies, you consent to have cookies, including cookies used by ITI, placed on your computer when you visit our Client’s websites.
Disclosure and Transfer of Information to Third Parties
Third parties perform tasks on our behalf and are contractually obligated not to disclose or use ITI User Information or Client User Data for any other purpose, and to employ adequate security measures to prevent unauthorized access to such data. ITI is not responsible in the event that Personally Identifiable Information is disclosed as a result of a breach or security lapse by any such third party.
Law Enforcement and Legal Process. ITI reserves the right to disclose any ITI Client Information or Client User Information (including Personally Identifiable Information) to: (i) comply with any law, regulation, or legal request; (ii) enforce, apply, or investigate breaches of the Terms of Use or other agreements; (iii) respond to client requests; or (iv) protect the rights, property, or safety of ITI, our employees, our users, or others.
Change of Control. If ITI, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired by another company or successor entity, ITI Client Information and/or Client User Data will be one of the assets transferred or acquired by the purchaser or successor. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any purchaser of or successor to ITI or its assets may continue to collect, use and disclose your information acquired prior to such transfer or acquisition as set forth in this policy.
Email Communications
We may contact you by e-mail or other equivalent electronic communications if you access ITI products or services. By registering or using ITI services, you specifically consent to the receipt of these e-mail or phone communications. If you do not want to receive emails or other communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions in the body of such communications or notify us by email at info@iti-global.com.
How We Protect Your Personal Information
ITI has implemented reasonable security mechanisms to protect ITI Client Information and Client User Data that is maintained on ITI’ servers from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Examples of these security mechanisms include limited and password-protected access, encryption on processed data, and SSL encryption to protect transmission of data.
However, please keep in mind that no security system is impenetrable. It may be possible for third parties to intercept or access ITI Client Information and Client User Data in spite of these measures. ITI cannot guarantee the security of your information and cannot be held responsible for unauthorized access to ITI client accounts.
Our Policy Toward Children
Our Site and Service is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 or from websites that are targeted to children under 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us as provided below. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete such information from our servers.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
ITI retains the discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make material changes to the way we collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information, we will notify you by posting a clear and prominent announcement on ITI or through a direct communication to your ITI account. For new users, the change or update will become effective upon posting. For existing users, the change or update will become effective 14 days after posting.
Use and disclosure of information we obtain is subject to the later of: (1) the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected or (2) any subsequent Privacy Policy of which you have constructive notice.
How to Contact Us
ITI welcomes any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices. Any such comments or questions should be submitted via e-mail to: info@iti-global.com or by first class mail, air mail, or overnight courier to:
ITI
5303 DuPont Circle
Milford, OH 45150
We will use reasonable efforts to respond promptly, within 10-20 business days, to requests, questions or concerns you may have regarding access to Personally Identifiable Information about you that we have collected. We may contact you for follow up information.
Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information should be directed to the ITI Office at the address given above. ITI will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information by reference to the principles contained in this Privacy Policy. For the avoidance of doubt, the dispute resolution procedures will be conducted in English.
Effective Date of this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of the Effective Date set forth at the top of this page.
SUBSCRIBE FOR ITI UPDATES
CareersContactData TransmissionHQ DirectionsLeadershipWebinars
